

Le Loc Thai Binh

Acting General Director at Meinhardt Viet Nam

Connect

♠ Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month





Connect

♠ Message

• • •

Le Loc Thai Binh · 3rd

Acting General Director at Meinhardt Viet Nam

Vietnam · 500+ connections · Contact info

Meinhardt Viet Nam

HCMC University of Architecture

About

Graduated from HCMC University of Architecture in 1999 and has nearly 20 years of experience in architectural planning, design, and project management. Participated in preparing design for various projects on a large scale in Kuwait & Vietnam, typically as Vinhomes Central Park Project (11 Towers, with height from 36-50 storeys/to ... see more

Activity

1,756 followers



Kính gửi: Quý Chủ đầu tư, quý Nhà thầu, và quý Đối tác của Meinhardt...

Le Loc shared this
50 Reactions • 5 Comments

See all activity

Experience

Acting General Director

Meinhardt Viet Nam · Full-time Sep 2020 – Present · 8 mos Vietnam

Manage the operation of the Company_ Establish business development strategy, monitor the deployment of the strategy and evaluate its efficiency periodically for timely adjustment to satisfy the business orientation and target of the Company

Deputy GD

Meinhardt Vietnam Jan 2015 – Sep 2020 · 5 yrs 9 mos Ho Chi Minh

Liaised with potential clients to establish relationship for finding new opportunities, project development;

Planned and oversaw new marketing initiatives;

Maintained fruitful relationship with local authorities, existing clients;

Undertook Principal position for all design projects;

... see more

Architectural Director

Meinhardt (Vietnam) Ltd. Sep 2009 – Jan 2015 · 5 yrs 5 mos

Vice Director

Branch of Ho Thieu Tri and Associates Co., Ltd. 2006 – Sep 2009 · 3 yrs Ho Chi Minh

Director – Enterprise 3

Industrial and Civil Design Joint Stock Company (IDCo)

1999 – 2006

· 7 yrs

146 Nguyen Cong Tru Street, District 1, HCMC

Education

HCMC University of Architecture

Bachelor of Architecture - BArch, Architecture 1993 – 1999

Skills & endorsements

Project Management . 22



Endorsed by 7 of Le Loc's colleagues at Meinhardt Group

Business Development . 15



Endorsed by 6 of Le Loc's colleagues at Meinhardt Group

Leadership . 10



Endorsed by 4 of Le Loc's colleagues at Meinhardt Group

Industry Knowledge

Feasibility Studies $_{\cdot\,40}$

Project Planning . 55

Construction Management . 36

```
Contract Management . 27
Design Management . 21
Construction . 19
Business Strategy . 16
Strategic Planning . 15
Management Consulting . 9
Civil Engineering . 7
Sustainability . 6
Procurement . 6
Architecture . 6
Value Engineering . 5
Budgets . 5
Engineering . 4
Project Estimation . 3
Business Planning . 3
Marketing Strategy . 3
Change Management
Project Coordination . 3
Cost Management . 3
Concrete . 3
Project Engineering . 3
```

```
CAD . 3
Project Control . 3
International Business . 2
Consulting . 2
Architectural Design . 1
New Business Development . 5
Tools & Technologies
AutoCAD . 24
Microsoft Office . 5
Microsoft Project . 5
Interpersonal Skills
Negotiation . 17
Management . 11
Contract Negotiation . 7
Team Leadership . 4
Contractors . 3
Customer Service . 1
Teamwork . 1
Other Skills 👩
Architectural Plans . 1
```

Construction Engineering

Construction Supervision

Construction Planning

Show less ^

Interests

Atkins

573,964 followers





_{bp} 2,845,509 followers

CONSTRUCTION & PROJECT MANAGERS - (I)

112,178 members

Standard Chartered Bank



1,337,256 followers

Government of Canada



314,869 followers

Australia Business and Professional Network



19,630 members

People also viewed



Phuong Thao Nguyen •3rd

HR & ADM Executive at Bureau Veritas Viet Nam

Connect

Mi Van •2nd

HR Director/ HRBP

Connect



Vũ Huỳnh Quốc ∙3rd

Design -Build Director / Technical Director

Connect



Mai Nguyen •3rd

Sourcing & Sales Engineer at AM Industries Viet Nam

Connect



Lâm Hoàng Văn •3rd

General Manager at EVORICH_NEEM

Connect

Show more Show more

People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



Nhi Duong

| Stuc | lent at | Ton I | Duc T | hand | Unive | rcity |
|------|---------|-------|-------|-------|-------|--------|
| Stuc | ieni ai | 1011 | Duc i | Hally | OHIVE | SISILY |

Connect

∨Show more



Add new skills with these courses



Revit 2021: Essential Training for Structure (Metric)

6,568 viewers



Construction Industry: Techniques and Technology

42,813 viewers



Cert Prep: Revit Structure Certified Professional

17,735 viewers

Show more on LinkedIn Learning



About

Accessibility

Talent Solutions

Community Guidelines

| Careers | |
|---------------------------------|---|
| Marketing Solutions | |
| Privacy & Terms ~ | |
| Ad Choices | |
| Advertising | |
| Sales Solutions | |
| Mobile | |
| Small Business | |
| Safety Center | |
| Questions? | |
| Visit our Help Center. | |
| Manage your account and privacy | |
| Go to your Settings. | |
| Select Language | |
| (Arabic) العربية | |
| LinkedIn Corporation © 2021 | |
| | |
| | C |

...